Ok, we're going to talk about apples. Ok. Ok.
Do you like apples? Yeah.
So, so, ok. How often do you eat apples? Once a week,
once a week? And how much is an apple in Japan? And it depends on the season.
Uh,
if it's
like summer season it's going to be very expensive.
But you mean are you talking about now or? Yeah, like right now, how much does an apple
say? Maybe about 100
1550 yen for an apple? Really? Yeah, that's kind of expensive.
Where do apples come from?
Aldi Prefectures?
Amoi?
Really is northern part in Japan. Ok.
All right. And what colors are apples? Red or green or yellow? Ok.
Which color is your favorite red?
Yeah.
Yeah. Actually I like the green apples. Really? I don't know.
I just in America we have sour green apples. Does it taste different?
Yeah. Like the red apples are sweet and the green apples?
They're very sour.
Yeah. So they're very nice.
One last thing. What can you make with apples? Apple juice, apple pie
and apple,
apple
tea?
Ok. And can you make apple pie?
No, not really.
Yeah, me neither. Ok, thanks, thanks.